Gerardo Munoz

San Antonio, TX 78245 (512) 986-1629

g.munozii@icloud.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/gerardo-mu%C3%B1oz-7b114819b/

GitHub: https://github.com/gmunoz94

Portfolio: https://gmunoz94.github.io/portfolio/

Summary

I am a hard working, ambitious individual with several years of optical industry experience, and I'm looking to transition into the field of Web Development. My peers would describe me as hard working and diligent. I love a challenge and finding solutions to complex problems/tasks

Technical Skills

- MySQL
- Bootstrap
- Node.js
- CSS
- HTML
- RESTful
- JavaScript

PROJECTS

Bill's PC | https://github.com/gmunoz94/pokeProj | https://gmunoz94.github.io/pokeProj/

- A simple application designed to allow users to choose, name, and build a moveset for Pokemon.
- In charge of the CSS and HTML building of the website. Also wrote the logic that helped with the navigation between pages.
- Tools/Languages
 - o Bulma CSS Framework
 - HTML5
 - Javascript
 - PokeAPI
 - Purgomalum

Password Generator | https://gmunoz94.github.io/passGenerator

- My first application I created. Intended to create secure passwords based on user defined inputs and choices.
- I was the sole creator of this application.
- Tools/Languages
 - o CSS
 - Javascript
 - o HTML5

EXPERIENCE

Dean Eastman State Farm, San Antonio, TX - Insurance Sales Rep

April 2021 - PRESENT

Omni Vision, San Antonio, TX - Optician

July 2018 - April 2021

I was hired as an optician and tasked with selling and styling patients in their frames. I then moved on to being the Lab Technician and cutting all of the jobs for the office. I used the Edger, Blocker, and Drill for drill mount frames. Was promoted to manager. Developed many promotions and internal solutions.

LensCrafters, Alpharetta, Ga/San Antonio, TX - Optician

September 2014 - July 2018

I was originally a retail associate where I would assess the customers needs and wants to make the best recommendations for them in terms of their eyewear. I then became a Sales Supervisor and oversaw the retail floor. I would deal with customer service issues as well as making sure the associates were meeting the standards set forth by corporate. I also learned the lab side of the job so that I could help in manufacturing the lenses.

EDUCATION

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development